James Ahn

portfolio / jamesahn.co

ux/ui designer Jamesahn0717@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/james-ahn (236)-512-9610

summary of qualifications

UX Design	HTML	Photoshop	Teamwork
UI Design	CSS	Illustrator	Problem Solving
Prototyping	Python	Premiere Pro	Time Management
Figma	InDesign	Lightroom	Self-Motivated

¹ years + of key experience in the travel industry, combined with a solid academic background specializing in user experience

3 years + of working in Figma with teammates and efficiently get work done with them in an effective pace

experience

Designer - Starterhacks at University of Waterloo

Jan 2019

Thought of and started on a prototype with a newly met group and designed the layout and wireframes for it. Once the wireframes were made, I reached out to mentors and other groups to user test it and get feedback from it to make it more intuitive and easier

UX/UI Design Intern - Tugolo

May 2019 - August 2019

Re-designed Tugolo's entire website using Figma to make it a more interactive and user friendly experience for its users. I worked with another designer and three developers that brought our designs to life. I focused more on the mobile designs as it was an essential part for Tugolo's target group. I started off with wireframes and moved to high fidelity models, user testing them to other workers and gaining valuable comments

UX/UI Designer - Tastebuds

Jan 2019 - present

Currently envolved in launching a startup and helping design for it. I am making adjustments on the current interface to give it a more simple and clean look. After these adjustments, I went out to ask for user feedback and modify it accordingly

education

Honours Global Business and Digital Arts - University of Waterloo

Sept 2017 - April 2021 Waterloo, ON

Exchange Program - Singapore University of Technology and Design

Sept 2019 - Dec 2019 Singapore

activites & interests

Snowboarding Camping Hiking Travelling

Photography Videography

Snowboarding

Participated in the snowboarding club in my high school and went to provincials and won 3rd place boys snowboarding and 1st place in mixed snowboarding

Travelling

Went on exchange to Singapore and travelled to 5 different countries, adding count to the 21 countries I've travelled to

Continously expanding my knowledge through experiencing different cultures

² years + of prototyping and design sprints for quick ideas